Why don't you come home step by step?
I saw you, you've been coming to me since yesterday in songs.
I don't know what happens to me. Come, I want to see you.
Come, I want to see you.
There's a paradise awaiting this desire.
I don't know how I'm going to attain it if I don't see you.
Come, I want to see you.
The summers are slipping away, leaving the city empty.
The looming winters are killing me.
I'm the rhyme of your lips.
You are the end of all wrongs.
Sounds good. I want to see you.
I want to see you.
I want to see you. And ...
Why don't you freeze time dancing with me
to the rhythm of that clave that knows
how to warm us up? Come, I want to see you.
Come, I want to see you.
I don't know if I'm the destiny
you have in mind.
Maybe I can be an excellent mistake in your life.
Come, I want to see you.
The stars are melting, warming hearts.
Companies are breaking down
investing in love.
I'm the rhyme of your lips.
You are the end of all wrongs.
Sounds good. I want to see you.
I want to see you. I want to see you.
It's that I want to see you.
Streetlights are already on.
I sent you the location.
No door is closed.
Just follow the song.
The one about the rhyme of your lips,
the one about the ending of all wrongs,
the one that sounds good, the one that says,
the one that says,
the one that says: I want to see you.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
Thank you for having us.
We are thrilled to be here today playing in
front of this emblematic desk.
This song is off my new record.
The song is called "Monte Adentro."
I hope you enjoy. Thank you.
One, two.
I'm coming back from the mountain within me,
passing through olive branches.
Even if promises go up in flames,
and it's hard for us to find our way back.
I'm bringing kindling for the fire.
So the candle doesn't go out.
A wind that gets rid of sand.
To erase the border
between you and me.
Between you and me.
I pour myself as spring waters,
a current broken for return.
I'm overflowing the riverbed in torrents
I don't know how to love in drops.
When memories are erased and details slip away,
may this encounter be eternal.
At least while it lasts.
Kindling for the fire.
So the candle doesn't go out.
A wind that gets rid of sand.
To erase the border.
Kindling for the fire. So the candle doesn't go out.
A wind that gets rid of sand.
To erase the border
between you and me.
Sweet. Thank you very much.
Allow me to present really quick my friends
who are playing with me today. Most of them
we've been playing for a lot of years together.
This fine young gentleman right here in the
piano, from Mexico.
Jos Parker. Please give it up.
I get to play with my favorite drummer.
He's José Andrés Márquez from Mexico on the drums.
And my old pal from way back from Houston, Texas.
But he is for me, kind of like a New York guy.
David Lizmi, right here. And the very talented, he's
playing guitar and sax today.
He plays more instruments,
but we don't have enough songs for that today.
Luisber del Río, from Mexico.
I was born and raised in the Dominican Republic
and my name is Alex.
Thank you for having me. Are there Dominicans here?
There's one? OK. This song is called "Un Cariñito."
One. Two. Three.
I've been dancing alone for a while.
Looking for a good way to frame the photo.
Lighting up the palo santo.
Taking care of the form, sharpening the craft.
I saw you pass by the window.
You turned the savannah into a jungle
with your little dress full of flowers.
I'd never seen any of those colors.
I did an amazing trick.
I tamed a tiger, a lion, an elephant.
I sing songs, I live off art.
Just to impress you.
I don't want to be rude.
Nor anything less than brave.
Let time settle into the groove.
Because, look, a little lovin' doesn't hurt anybody.
A little lovin' doesn't hurt anybody.
I did an amazing trick.
I tamed a tiger, a lion, an elephant.
I sing songs, I live off art.
Just to impress you.
A lightbulb turned on in the labyrinth of my heart.
If you tell me to follow you, I'll go to the ends of the Earth.
To the heart of the palm tree, to the city,
to the mountain, jumping into an ocean cave, wherever,
but with you. Wherever, but with you.
Wherever, but with you.
With you, with you, with you.
Yes, yes, that's right my love.
A lightbulb turned on in the labyrinth of my heart.
For this song we have a very,
very special guest for you guys.
Coincidently, she was around the area
and we invited her to sing with us today.
This is very special. This is very special.
Please give it up for the one and only.
From Veracruz, Mexico. Silvana Estrada.
Actually, this is — this is full circle for us
because, well, Silvana is not new to this space.
If you haven't seen Silvana's Tiny Desk,
I would recommend you stop watching this one.
Go watch hers and then maybe come back.
Thank you.
Give it up for Josh. This is the first song
Silvana and I sung when we met way back, 10
years ago.
This is an old one. Thank you for having us.
Boys, ready?
You, in the center of the city.
Alone, among so many people, like a butterfly from the arrabal
that gets lost and wants to return.
Wants to return.
I keep on rowing endlessly, can't make out the shore.
Like a strange sea creature, adrift.
Who doesn't care where it's going.
Doesn't care where it's going.
But the day I find you on my path
I'll drop everything.
Gather my things and get lost with you.
I'll get lost with you.
I fall in love easily.
But what's more surprising is how little it lasts.
I don't recognize happiness if it's not yours.
But the day I find you on my path
I'll drop everything, gather my things and get lost with you.
I'll get lost with you.
But the day I find you on my path
I'll drop everything, gather my things and get lost with you.
I'll get lost with you.
Wow. Good!
I love you, my friend!